imenu360.com 2019-07-22

# Privacy Policy - Online Food Ordering Platform System | iMenu360

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices of iMenu360 Inc.(We), which operates a private label online ordering systems for clients across the world. Protecting privacy is important to us and below is the policy we have enacted.

Information Collection

We collect information volunteered by consumers when they register and place orders on our Web site. The information we collect through registration and order placement is used to provide the services specified on our Web site. From time to time, we may solicit additional personal and demographic information, for market research purposes, in the form of surveys or polls. Participation in market research surveys by our customers is entirely optional and at their discretion. We also store information such as page views, computer IP addresses and other statistics in the form of logs. These logs are used solely to enhance the technical performance of our Web site.

Information Sharing 

In order to process your food order, we must share the following information every time you place an order with a restaurant: your name, delivery address, food order and credit card information (if applicable). We restrict this information flow to only the bare minimum elements required to prepare and fulfill your orders. Occasionally, we may voluntarily share, sell or rent aggregated (non-personal) market research data with 3rd party partners and vendors. This information does not contain personally identifiable information and is shared for the purposes of enhancing our service. We may present offers to you on behalf of third party partners. If you accept an offer, we will share your name, address and credit card information with this third party. We will not share this information without your consent.

Credit Cards.

As a policy, credit card information is NOT stored with iMenu360. If a restaurant subscribes for secure card storage facility with the PCI compliant credit card service partners AND you opt to take advantage of it, iMenu360 provides a seamless integration for accessing credit card information that is stored with the credit card service partner. If and when you opt to store the card information, your credit card data is ALWAYS stored with PCI compliant credit card service partners that adhere to the prescribed credit card industry's electronic storage security standards.

Customer Communication 

Our customer service representatives may use your telephone number, e-mail address and instant messenger ID to notify you of the status of your order as necessary and appropriate. Upon request, we provide Web site visitors with access to transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases or amounts and types of purchases) and contact information (e.g., name, address and phone number) we maintain about them. From time to time, we may use the information collected to send special offers on behalf of 3rd party partners or vendors (including restaurants) participating in our service. However, we do not share your information with the restaurant other than the information necessary to conduct business as stated above.

E-mail/ Anti-Spam

We do not purchase bulk e-mail addresses nor do we use the services of bulk e-mail companies for promoting our service. This means we will not distribute, sell or rent your e-mail address to any third party. Additionally, our e-mail servers do not relay e-mail destined for non-local domains.

Return/Refund Policy

If you are not satisfied with your order, please contact the restaurant directly and include the order number. All sales are final unless order problems/issues are confirmed with the restaurant and the restaurant determines if a refund is required. All order problem/issue inquiries must be received within 24 hours of the order date listed on your order confirmation email. All refunds will be handled by the restaurant directly and not iMenu360.com.

Security Policy

Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet

Do Not Track:

This service does not contain links to other websites. The information collected is made available only to the restaurant in which the order was placed. There are no tracking signals and iMenu360 does not respond to requests for such information from other websites. By using this App, your information is exposed only to iMenu360. Third parties do not have access and do not perform tracking.

Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please email [contactus@imenu360.com](mailto:contactus@imenu360.com) and put privacy policy in subject line. If you need to change personal information we have collected, please use the same email to request a change.
